We are deeply indebted to you, our honorable mentors
And since we entered this school, years have already passed
As we reminisce about the days we spent here,
we realize how time flies
Now is the time for us to part
To move ahead, we say goodbye
We've gotten along well caring about each other
How grateful I am to have such schoolmates
Even after we part for each way,
let's not forget this meeting and feeling
To be full-fledged ones and successful in each way,
let's strive for what each wants
Now is the time for us to part
Move ahead! We say goodbye
We've gotten used to the school days here and put our all into them,
like as an old saying "Under the light of fireflies, and reflected light from piled snow"
We'll never forget each moment of them,
all through the years we spent in this school
Now is the time for us to part
To move ahead, we say goodbye
Move ahead, we say goodbye!