Perhaps it’s just my imagination, only in my heart
but how is it that my shirt has shrunk?
I don’t know how to convey it! In front of my mirror
It’s like I’m trying to be a 1-man tsukkomi
It’s sort of good, definitely
But I just noticed the reason
for this trend of growth
I’ve got kind of a bad feeling
I have a weakness for sweets
as is typical of my being a lady
But after being so careless in just one regard,
I’m starting to learn the strain of this piling up
Oh yeah! Burn it off!
to get closer to the girl you want to be
Still not satisfied! Get rid of it!
so just give us a little leeway, Mr. Calorie!
Read the room!
You’re not welcome here!
I don’t want to ride around in that box
I’m sealing it away in some corner of my psyche
There’s bad news from my test results
Don’t push it with those numbers, NO!
Hey now, why is that? Isn’t it funny?
That girl’s a fool for snacking, but
keep that formula you made with a slurry powder
Seriously!? What’d you say? Tell me your secret!
Oh yeah! How can we lose!
I’m always looking back at the boys I know
Still not satisfied! Get rid of it!
so we really just need a little mercy, Mr. Calorie!
Always the same thing
I’m tormented by you
But I can always stay in good spirits
thanks to you
So you have my thanks for doing this
Nevertheless, I did a little too much!
Oh yeah! Burn it off!
to get closer to the girl you want to be
Still not satisfied! Get rid of it!
so just give us a little leeway, Mr. Calorie!
Read the room!
You’re not welcome here!
I’m none of your concern!