Kuramoto Speech
Now, we'll have a speech from Kuramoto Mitsuru, the Principal of Sakura Gakuin.
Congratulations on your graduation
Today, on a way to this venue,
I walked the slope road
'Sakura-zaka'
which leads to
the entrance of Sakura Gakuin
The cherry trees were in full bloom
it was so beautiful
I felt we can have this ceremony at a very opportune time
Seeing cherry blossom had made me think
Now Spring has come...
It's getting warm...
Soon we'll have a cherry-blossom viewing...
But in these few years,
the cherry blossom make me think of
the graduation of Sakura Gakuin
and that make me
very emotional
While seeing the cherry blossom,
I recollected
the first impression of
4 of you graduates
Mizuno was so short,
and was
always spinning round
and chanting something strange
I felt
'Is she OK?'
And Kikuch also was short
but she was emitting
an atmosphere that she can see right through everything...
I felt she reads me like a book
I thought 'Is it possible THIS small girl being like that?'
'What the hell is she going to be?'
When I met Taguchi for the first time,
she was like a doll
and was absent-minded
so I thought
'Err...there is still no soul installed into this doll...'
'Is she all right?'
And Notsu...
maybe because she had been already a middle schooler,
I felt she was over-familiar with me
She was like an old hand
with a lot of experience
and I felt
something is wrong
A while later, I heard
Notsu had been very nervous
she was doing her best,
to find out what's her charm,
what lies in herself
And I named her as the Talk-Chairperson
I know,
she has been in
a tough year
Today I heard
you saying on the stage
'At first, Koubaibu was terrible'
It was really so, and I felt very uneasy
but you made a great improvement
Today, your MCing was really adorable
And,
as of Taguchi,
I saw a soulless doll
gradually get a wonderful soul
and, as the Spirit Chairperson,
she really stirred up
everyone's spirits
And your performance was awesome
I've been watching
Sakura Gakuin
from the very beginning
and two of the founding members
Mizuno and Kikuchi
are graduating after a long
5 years
it makes me
very emotional
As you know
these two girls
have come through everything of Sakura Gakuin
since they were 5th graders
There have been a lot of things
They have got over a lot of things
And furthermore
And a club activity
they've been playing
made an unbelievable success
and they've made
the world their stage
But even in
such a sensation
two of them never
put Sakura Gakuin activities aside
I'm deeply impressed
I've kept watching you
and found
the meaning,
the significance of Sakura Gakuin
In your growth period --
when you make great improvement
physically and mentally,
you are burdened
with heavy tasks
and you must overcome one task by another
I know you've got tons of problems and troubles
but you yourself had decided to be here because you love performing
so all of you have never be discouraged
That is the essence
of Sakura gakuin, I think
And that nature
enables you to improve
a lot, in a
short period
Well,
we, human being
use only 10% of
potential ability
of our brain
90% of the ability is inactive
But,
in a specific situation
by an extraordinary efforts
we can activate
the latent power of our brain
I think
you have activated,
unlike ordinal people,
20% or 25% of your brain
Unless, you can't achieve these amazing performance
Don't you think so?
Fukei-sans
To dance
such an elaborated choreography
while singing
and to have a talk just after dancing...
You did it
You must be proud of yourselves
It's just amazing
I think you've already been turning into 'Super'
I believe 'the days of women' is coming to Japan
A bright future, peaceful world will arrive
being lead by women
In the future,
there will be many female opinion leaders
and they take initiative
in making this world better
And when
you study the career
of female opinion leaders
you'll find
'What?'
'Is she a graduate of Sakura Gakuin?'
'And this one also is!?'
That's my dream
and I think it'll really happen
I'm looking forward to the future
So please don't be hesitate
to make a big impact to the world after your graduation
You don't need to worry about what people say.
because everyone here
knows what you've done in Sakura Gakuin
And everyone can't help being on your side,
cannot help but support you
Do you agree?
Please keep supporting them
after their graduation
And remaining members...
keep trying your best
As you know, there will remain really few students
It's true!
I'm very worried about what will come
So 4 of you,
Please come and give them good advice
Congratulations on your graduation
Thank you for your attention, this is all I have to say
It was Principal Kuramoto Mitsuru
Congratulations!