Graduation diploma, Okada Megumi-dono.
You have mastered singing, dancing and inspirations.
This is to certify that the above-mentioned has completed the prescribed elementary course of Sakura Gakuin.
March on Heisei 27 year. Principal of Sakura Gakuin, Kuramoto Mitsuru.
Congratulations!
Graduation diploma, Yamaide Aiko-dono.
The remainder of the text is the same as in the previous certificate.
Congratulations!
Graduation diploma, Kikuchi Moa-dono.
You have mastered singing, dancing and inspirations.
This is to certify that the above-mentioned has completed the prescribed all course of Sakura Gakuin.
In accordance with the school regulation of Sakura Gakuin, I hereby certify that you took the first step to the Superlady.
March on Heisei 27 year. Principal of Sakura Gakuin, Kuramoto Mitsuru.
Congratulations!
Graduation diploma, Taguchi Hana-dono.
The remainder of the text is the same as in the previous certificate.
Congratulations!
Graduation diploma, Notsu Yunano.
The remainder of the text is the same as in the previous certificate.
Congratulations!
Graduation diploma, Mizuno Yui-dono.
The remainder of the text is the same as in the previous certificate.
Congratulations!