Hello everyone!!!!!
We are, 'a unit limited to girls in growth-period', Sakura Gakuin! Please treat us well!
Yes, we have finally made it to NHK hall.
It’s amazing, isn’t it?
Everyone on the third floor, can you see us clearly?
Thank you!!
Everyone on the second floor, are you excited?
Thank you!
Everyone on the first floor, are you excited?
Thank you !
And finally...
NHK hall, how are you?
Wow! Thank you for you making loud noise!
There’s a lot of people here in NHK hall but...
this time, people are not just watching here.
We’re also having live viewings in 22 different movie theaters!!
YAYYYY
Wait, since people are watching at the movies
that means that they're eating popcorn while watching, right?
It's amazing. I'm jealous...
To everyone that’s eating their popcorn carelessly
are you Fukeis excited?
I heard them! I definitely hear them!
I don’t know if you’ve realised...
that on the movie screen, we look fatter to everyone
Ah! I don’t like that...
I became fat recently too...
You became fat recently?
Yes, in January in the new year
Well, for girls like us who have gained weight, we have made that song
With that said, to those Fukeis that think that they’ve gained weight recently,
You feel a bit obese,
You have these thoughts secretly in your heart.
Please sing this next song with us!
Please listen to: Gokigen! Mr. Toropikarori!