Well, we've played club units performances as an annual event
How do you feel about them?
Thank you very much
They all were awesome....especially Mini-pati medley...
Do you realize? All of the Mini-pati songs were played on the medley
As many as seven songs!
Amazing!
And the Pro-wrestling Circle...What was that?!
Your making appearance on the stage....just cool!
I was so impressed that Kiyono-san really came...it's fantastic
It was like a true pro-wrestling match
At last, Sakura Gakuin has invited a professional announcer.
Yes, The Pro came!
Too cool!
BTW, Does Kiyono-san have something to do from now?
No. He came just for this
Really? Just for this?
Yes, he came here just for this
It's amazing
Thank you for coming
Now, I want to ask something to the audience in the 2nd and the 3rd floor
Did you notice that there were a logo mark on the center of the ring?
Wow!
In fact, the logo mark is designed by combining logos of Sakura Gakuin and New Japan Pro Wrestling
The logo mark was on the ring!
But, I think the Pro-wrestling Circle tend to spend too much money. It's over budget.
Yes. When you appeared, too much CO2 gas was released
You must know, CO2 gas costs something
But, Koubaibu also used bazooka-thing.
Bazooka was good
You both spent money.
But listen to me...Pro-wrestling Circle spent Kiyono-san's fee,
CO2 fee and the ring fee
They spent too much, didn't they?
Also, the belt cost something
And the costume
The costume was a reuse
We wore them the other day
Going back to the bazooka story,
The Tees were launched from the bazooka
Who got those Tees?
Wow! congratulations!
The bazooka we used at the interlude of the song
was so powerful that it carried a Tee to the 2nd floor
The Tee is with our autograph on it
Yunano was almost blown off by the recoil of the bazooka
Because Yunano is too slender
I'm sorry I was so surprised that I screamed aloud
Sorry for my making big noise
Shirasaki, didn't you steal an autographed-Tee?
No! Never! I could find 4 Fukei-sans who got the Tees
Really?
Well, and the Baton Club...maybe it sounds strange that I say this...but the members twirled the batons very well, didn't they?
Thank you very much
Personallly, I love the choreo of Sara-chan singing "Daisuki dayo"
Yes it's very cute
The posing comes from the former Baton Club -- the same with the Sugisaki Nene-chan's posing
Really?
The line was sung by Nene-don?
Yes, that's it
Anyway, you looked super kawaii
Thank you
Well, let's go to the next song
We'll make good use of the 2nd floor of the setting in the next song
Please listen to -- Sleep Wonder