Thank you very much
Well, we've performed Sleep Wonder
How was that?
Thank you
By the way, from the beginning to the very end, Taguchi Hana-san as a cat didn't show us the way
You are ruthless!
errr...I don't know the way neither
Oh! You don't?
Even if I knew it, I couldn't tell...the story would go into a mess
In this song, we make good use of the 2nd floor...so I felt audience in the 2nd and the 3rd floor a little closer
I'm pleased to play this song here
Thank you very much
And, since the club activity part, the setting of the stage changed a little
Did you notice the change?
wo...it seems difficult
Really? You didn't notice?
Oh my...
Well, now I tell the truth
Look at the background
Sparkling!
Till then, the background presented an aurora
And since the club activity part, it changed into this starry sky!
It's beautiful
Recently, Yui loves to see night sky
This background is really good for Planet Episode 008, isn't it?
I hoped to present starry sky at the song, and teachers made it come true
Wow! Did you ask to do it?
Ah, I didn't
It's amazing. He knew your untold intention
Your intention reached somehow
I hoped to see shooting stars
And I've watched the background carefully
but there was no shooting star at all
Yunano was looking for Winter Triangle
You somehow can find a kind of triangle...
ah...I see
In a very creative way?
Maybe...there is a triangle
And, we played Planet Episode 008 which fit very well to the starry sky
The song is one of our 'Let's learn' series
So, just before the graduation, I think we've learned something
This song was really helpful to me in my exam
I became 3rd grader, and I had a year-end exam
It's not Sakura Gakuin story, right?
And there were questions about planets
Everyone, please try to remember the lyric
We hope so
Well, now we are going to play the next song
Till now, we've played cheerful, 2014nendo-like songs
From now, we'll play the songs which show our minds, present feelings exactly
Those who have supported us in this one year, please listen to them remembering several things in this year
Please listen to....Heart no Hoshi!