Thank you very much
It's an nice tune, absolutely!
I'm so impressed.
It's so cute!
Fukei-sans, it's a little too early to cry
Too early!
When Saki heard this song for the first time, I cried too
The lyric and music are awesome, and the choreo is cute....It is made just to make us cry, don't you think so?
You are talking like an old lady.
Like a lady,yes
Or just a Fukei-san
I love Yunano's line "Ikanakya〜"
I see. It's true
Really?
For Yunano....it's a less favorite line
Why? It's really cute.
It's embarrassing....but the teachers told me you have to do it
There is an image that Yunano sings very straightforwardly
So, the singing in a very Idol-like way is...
It's my very first and last Idol-like singing
very cute and fresh for us
Thank you very much
Moa and Yui-san, how do you feel about this song?
The lyric is super good
It was written by Inaba Emi-san, and the lyric are really great
It expresses our feelings exactly...so it's very nice to sing this song
I see
To sing a song with only the graduating members has been a tradition since the year of Ayami-chan, Ayaka-chan and Airin.
Yes it's true
So, I'm pleased we could succeed the tradition. And the color of the song fits 4 of us exactly. Don't you think so?
Indeed! This song is super peaceful
At the beginning....please listen to the intro...you can hear a bird singing
Yes. It's a very morning-like song.
I got up with this song in this morning
It sounds good
It's good. A bird is a symbol of peace.
Everyone, please make this song your alarm music
You can really get up comfortably
It was an unveiling -- and our last playing of this song. I'm very pleased we could show you at last.
It was fun
Thank you very much
Well, the song made us sentimental and I can see several Fukei-sans crying...
It's too early
But we want to enjoy more. Fukei-sans, are you ready to get hyper together with us?
Thank you very much
With keeping this excitement, let's play the next song!