Thank you very much.
Can the undergraduates please say some words to the graduating members?
Hai
Saki remembers the open class event; "Study of Calligraphy"
At the event, I wrote "I want to carry more, please send me more"
Saki's feelings were reached.
I have a lot of worries for next year, but
We are going to do our best, so
Please keep watching over us.
Thank you very much!
Moa-chan
Yui-chan
Hana-chan
Yunano-chan
To all you 3rd graders, Megu looks up to the four of you.
Sometimes I try to catch up to you guys but I'm not able to.
Conversely, I often mess up in the process.
I'm sorry.
But Megu will try her best to improve the Sakura Gakuin that we all love.
So cheer us on.
Also, please let us keep calling the four of you our nice big sisters.
Thank you for today.
This year's graduates taught us many things
I myself feel like I've matured a lot.
For the next year's members, I would like to teach our underclassmen the same way the graduates of this year have taught me.
So please cheer on- ahhhh
So please keep watching over us.
Thank you.
I feel sad that the four of you will graduate, but
I will try my best to show the audience that Sakura Gakuin is still good.
So relax and go ahead and graduate
Also
I mean it in a good way. In a good way!
Taguchi: You-
You're mistaken.
That's not what I meant.
I really mean it in a good way.
So,
Thank you for everything from the start.
I love you all, really.
Thank you very much.
Um,
Even though Sara only had one year to do activities with the four year 3’s, unlike everyone else.
There were a lot of fun memories, and frustrating memories,
But because we shared them together,
All of these memories will always be treasures to me.
Thank you very much!
There's only one thing Rinon has to say to the four 3rd graders.
Yui, thank you.
Yunano, thank you.
Hana, thank you.
Moa, thank you.
To be honest, it has not sunk in yet that 4 of you are really graduating.
I have no idea what to say.
So,
I want to express my gratitude to the four of you, and I hope it is received successfully.
Also, to those Fukei-sans who've supported us in this year,
From here on. From here on? That sounds a bit weird now.
Thank you very much.
And please watch over us next year too.
Hai
Very well, now let's listen to what the four graduates would like to say, one at a time.
To be honest, when I entered Sakura Gakuin,
I had a lot of frustration and there were times I would want to quit.
But, to see the smiles of the Fukeis,
As well as seeing the members support each other,
I was able to move forward despite having strict lessons.
To Yunano, they are my treasure.
I am very glad to have met everyone.
Thank you very much!
Hai
When I was in grade 6, I transferred into Sakura Gakuin,
And did many activities in these 4 years as member of Sakura Gakuin.
Also in these 4 years, I've been taken care of by many people.
And also,
Today…today as well as myself graduating, I would also like to graduate from my negative character.
Yup.
Thank you.
So I thought I should do my best, and you know what?
Haaa!
Ohh!
Eh!
Today is the last day for Sakura Gakuin’s Hana but,
From today forward, I will be a student of Torahime Ichiza-san, a Young Tiger,
And I would like to do my best.
So finally,
To the audience in NHK Hall-
I love you!
Thank you very much!
With that said, we are running low on time
In order to beco…
This is bad
Ah! It’s bad
I will put something together with the little time I have
I have many friends, teachers, graduates, and Fukeis that I can believe from my heart, and I love with all my heart.
If there’s ever painful times ahead, I will take these 5 years and turn it into strength.
After today, I wish for my dreams as YUIMETAL, and as Mizuno Yui to come true.
I would appreciate everyone’s support.
Please watch over next year's Sakura Gakuin.
Thank you very much for everything up until today!
To be honest, I do not want to graduate.
Sakura Gakuin is a place that is warm, and all of you Fukeis made it a place where you can welcome me home.
We would like to see what’s ahead.
We would be happy if everyone watched over the 2015 Sakura Gakuin nendo.
Please let me say one final thing.
SAKURA GAKUIN IS THE BEST!
Thank you very much!
Thank you, thank you, thank you very much for attending today!
And so! This was Sakura Gakuin 2014!
Bye bye!
Thank you very much!