Soredewa shussekiwo torimasu
Now, I'll call the roll
Doumo Sakura Gakuin tannin no Mori HAYASHI desu
Welcome! I am Mori Hayashi, homeroom teacher of Sakura Gakuin
2014nendomo shimekukurino raibu, minasan, moetsukiru junbiwa dekiteimasuka?
Here goes the last concert in 2014nendo. Everyone, are you ready to challenge your limit in enjoying yourself?
Raibu byuuingu wa miteruka?
Are you watching via Live Viewing?
Moetsukiru junbiwa...Nanda nanda? Omaera -- Hayaku Hayaku! Shusseki totte...Shusseki torukara
Are you ready...What? You girls, what are you doing? Hurry up! Let's make a call...I now call the roll
Minna junbishite, junbishite... Naninaninani? Hako ga nai? Hako aru. Hako, askoni arukara. Hayaku totte
Every girls, prepare for... What? You can't find the box? There are boxes. They are over there. Take them in a hurry
Minna sorottenno? Minna sorotteru? Nanka Ninzuu Tarinaiyo... Hokano Menbaa wa?
All members here? I think someone is missing. Whre are other members?
Detekonai? Detekonai? Moriagaru Junbi Dekitennokana kore?
Not everyone yet? Still waiting? Are you really ready to challenge your limit?
Ah, kita kita kita. Sorotta sorotta. Yoshi, minna, shusseki toruzo. Moariagatte ikukarana
Oh, here they are. Everyone is ready now. Well, girls, I'll call the roll.  Let's have a blast!
Minasan hajikete ikuzo! Kore ga kotoshi no Sakura Gakuin da!
Everyone, let's get hyper! Here’s this year’s Sakura Gakuin!