Now...I shall call the roll!
Welcome! I am Mori Hayashi, homeroom teacher of Sakura Gakuin.
Here goes the last concert in 2014 Nendo.
Everyone, are you ready to challenge your limits in enjoying yourself?
Is everyone from the Live Viewing watching?
Are you ready?... What? Girls, what are you doing? Hurry up!
Take your spot...I am about to call the roll!
Everyone, get ready!... What? You can't find the box?
The box is there! It's over there! Hurry up and take it!
Is everyone here? I think some members are missing! Where are the other members?
Not everyone yet? Still waiting? Are you really ready to challenge your limits?
Oh, here they are. Everyone is ready now!
Well, girls, I'll call the roll! Let's have a blast!
Everyone, let's get hyper! Here’s this year’s Sakura Gakuin!