Touji
Cherry blossoms line the path of the street I walk by every day.
The tiny buds are starting to blossom one by one,
it feels like they are celebrating each one of us as we take our next step.
At last this year, March has come to the day of graduation, hasn't it?
We performed many shows, open classes, release events, and the lessons we rehearsed over and over.
Every memory is a precious treasure, as I recall.
Even as I read this Touji, I feel like it is a dream.
There is part of me that believes I will still be in Sakura Gakuin forever.
When tomorrow comes, there will no longer be the 10 of us.
That is probably when I will truly realise that I graduated, and the emotions will start flooding in suddenly.
Yui and myself are the only ones here from the inaugural year of Sakura Gakuin. We were so little.
Everyone watched over us, as we were still in 5th grade.
Now we are the upperclassmen.
Sakura Gakuin started with nothing, no shows, schedules, or releases planned when we started.
We now have more songs than we can perform in one year,
and we are in this big hall with our graduation ceremony.
I could not imagine such things back then.
But it is not just the 10 of us who made this happen.
The Senpai's, as graduates of Sakura Gakuin, have paved the way.
First off, I would like to show my appreciation for the Senpai's who have graduated before us.
Sakura Gakuin has overcome many obstacles, as we have grown.
This year's graduating class all entered at different times.
In 2011 we got Hana, in 2012 we got Yunano, as they transferred in we became four.
At last year's graduation, we carried on the will of Senpai,
but it was also a start filled with hesitation, as we all had different roles and had to build a good relationship.
Every year, we perform in the summer, TIF, is the first big obstacle.
Yui and I, due to our extracurricular actives overseas, could only appear by video.
But with Hana and Yunano at the core,
and the help of graduates Marina-chan and Raura-chan,
the members all pulled together, and put on a very Sakura Gakuin performance.
While in America, we talked all the time, "How are they doing?".
There wasn't a day that went by that we did not think about everyone working hard back in Japan.
That is when we felt strongly, we may be apart but our heart is one.
Because we experienced that we could not be with the other members.
We started to value every day that we spend.
We wanted to do as much as possible with the limited time we have. This I felt strongly.
...and again, this year we challenged ourselves with a lot of club activities.
Hana and Rinon, I can't believe they made the Pro Wrestling Circle.
I was jealous watching the douki* support each other, as you guys shined brightly. [*Douki - people who enter an organization around the same time]
Rinon, you look after everyone, you really observe everyone.
Your partner is going now, but there are three in your class to support each other.
Yunano & Shirai Saki were Koubaibu.
The two of you, with perfect timing filled the venue with laughter. It made me happy.
ShiraSaki, you know the charm of Sakura Gakuin from the inside and outside, always seriously thinking about it.
Next year again, please do things that will make Fukei's happy.
Sara & Aiko, who joined the Baton club.
It was your first time with the baton, but I was amazed at how fast you guys improved.
You guys must have practiced a lot, when we didn't see you.
Aiko, out of all the members you have to travel the most with your commute.
You're only in elementary school, you work so hard.
It is cool, that you can say what is on your mind, clearly.
Don't forget that honesty as you move into Jr. High.
Spunky and serious, Sara.
You're quick to think, and the Fukei's still have a lot more charm to see.
Next year I want to see more of that.
Saki, this year you must've had a lot of frustrations.
But your dedication to your love of singing, and kindness,
everyone around you understands this about you.
Next year, I know you will be standing here with a big smile after you have given it your all. I believe that.
Megu. Your first stage at the transfer-in ceremony you should've been nervous,
but you surprised us with your improv. We were all talking about it.
You're cute and we like pampering you. I am proud of my little sister.
We are only 15. The time we spent at Sakura Gakuin, may just be a moment in our long lifespan.
But we might say, it was everything to us, that is how fulfilling our time here was.
2014 members, the memories we made with the ten, every single one is a treasure.
Truthfully, I still want to spend more time with everyone.
With this 10, I want to do more.
But we are going towards our goal of becoming a Super Lady.
We must look forward and move on.
Rinon, Saki, ShiraSaki, Sara, Aiko and Megu.
With all of you, I have full faith, to entrust you with the next Sakura Gakuin.
What kind of message you will deliver, what kind of flavour Sakura Gakuin you will build.
Starting tomorrow, I will be watching over you with excitement.
Principal Kuramoto sensei, who showed us a world we never knew. The road of a Super lady.
Mori Sensei, who brought out my individuality, which I did not realise.
The staff teachers, who helped us grow, you were always close by, sometimes strict, sometimes kind.
Behind the scenes, there were people hustling for us, everyone on the Staff,
and everywhere and anytime, those who supported us…
a little oya baka Fukei san. [*Oya baka - a term used for new parents, who are foolish and see their children as angels who can do nothing wrong or parents who are proud of their children almost foolishly]
We want to say what we are feeling...
I want to say with the world's biggest Thank You.
Thank You. Truly, thank you for everything till now.
The four of us will etch into our hearts what we learned here.
Being proud that we are graduates of Sakura Gakuin, as we walk our path.
Please continue to support us and the 2015 Sakura Gakuin.
27th year of the Hesei Era, March 29th in 2014 school year.
Sakura Gakuin Graduate Representative, Kikuchi Moa.