Today, there are a lot of Fukei's attending.
I thank you from the bottom of my heart.
So with that, this is Sakura Gakuin 2014 nendo.
We are going to hand out the graduation diplomas.
Now then, students, enter.
Next, graduates, enter
Bow!
Sit!
Now, Principal Kuramoto Mitsuru will hand out the graduation diplomas.
Elementary school, 6th grade, Okada Megumi
Hai!
Elementary school, 6th grade, Yamaide Aiko
Next, Jr High graduates.
Jr. High, 3rd year, Kikuchi Moa
Jr. High, 3rd year, Taguchi Hana
Jr. High, 3rd year, Notsu Yunano
Jr. High, 3rd year, Mizuno Yui
So then, to give the student's Souji [a speech given to the graduates, showing appreciation and congratulations]
Sakura Gakuin, entrance year 2011, Jr High, 2nd year, Rinon Isono
Next, to give the Graduation Toji
Sakura Gakuin, Jr. High 3rd year.
Hai!
To be represented by Student Council President Moa Kikuchi.
Now, Sakura Gakuin Principal Kuramoto will give a Shukuji [a celebratory speech]
Sorry, let me say a few words, excuse me…
First of all, to all watching the live stream, it is now your chance for a bathroom break.
Go now. For those here, please stay.
If I see it in the corner of my eye, my ego may bruise.
Well, so let me say my honest thoughts.
Eh... this year, I was really worried about these four graduates.
As some may already know,
when I banter, there is one who cries easily.
We're performing live, and they lost the will to fight.
When I was over enthusiastic, there was one who would shut down emotionally.
One who was proud of her impersonations, who would leave the audience at a loss.
Truthfully... my job is to MC, in the role of a teacher,
so I was really worried this year.
But the year has passed.
Especially in these few months, these four can now be on stage and say what they want.
During the liver performances they respond and started bantering back.
I'm going to say it.
That made me really happy.
How do I say this...
I think a lot of you may have not been comfortable with my banter.
But you gained the courage and stepped up.
Yes, to me that is my treasure.
Yes, I know, every year, just as it is getting fun, we come to the graduation ceremony.
My emotional milk crepe is all limp and floppy.
So as a teacher, I thought about this very hard, and came up with this.
So I know formally that you are all graduating.
But in my heart, you are all held back a year.
I know I need to face the music,
but I am worried about all of you.
You get it.
I am sure the Fukei's understand...
as well as all of the staff.
If you are ever in trouble we will all come to your aid.
Well, even after you graduate, I'll still be your teacher,
and I'll still banter and bring out your individual charm...
I hope we can have that kind of relationship.
That is what I feel.
Of course this applies to all the previous graduates as well.
I still watch the "Merengue no Kimochi" with butterflies in my stomach,
You know. So, I want you to rely on me.
Although if the Nurse comes to depend on me, I'm not sure what I can do.
So in my mind, all of you,
I still have not put the seal of approval on your graduation certificate in my heart.
You know, right now,
they say you are all grown up... but you carry a lot on your little shoulders.
The weight you carry...
I sometimes feel that you should share that burden.
I'm sure a lot of people feel the same way... I know staff does.
Sorry, I am saying things, still holding on to you…
So what I want to really say is "Let me still act as your teacher", that is all.
So with that, congratulations on your graduation.
Please remember me…
So with that, I'm sorry it's always me speaking last.
Did you come back from your bathroom break?
Everyone in the live viewing?
Truthfully, I derailed the conversation, but…
Eh... so with this, we're going to perform now...
Hey, all the tears stopped flowing!
That was my intention.
So go back and change,
entertain the Fukei-san till the very end!
And so...
Graduating Class, you are dismissed!
Everyone, please give a round of applause.
With that, the 2014 Graduation Ceremony has ended.
Everyone bow.