Cherry blossoms swaying in the wind, steady stream of sunshine
Morning mist glittering a light blue, thanks yet again today
I stood still in front of the mirror, committing this pain to memory
Today is the last day I’ll ever see myself in this familiar school uniform, huh?
As I unravel the loneliness caught up inside my buttons,
I looked hard directly ahead, opening up the door to my future
My present to you, “Graduation toss”
Whenever the treasures I've stored in the music box lights up,
I’ll always be able to remember everyone
If the destiny that reminds us of the flow of time is showing us each our separate paths,
then I’ll accept that even if it means being alone
I’ll go past this impulse called “setting off”
Hey my friends, yeah my friends, dear my friends
“My Graduation Toss”, I’ll begin walking ahead
Hey my friends, yeah my friends
Without being able to say a word, I sent off friends last year around this time
Yeah dear my friends
Tonight I just might fall asleep clutching my diploma
When I happen to look up, cherry blossoms are fluttering in the sky
Even after graduation, our hearts’ bonds don’t change
Tying our dreams together is this “Graduation Toss”
Just like the constellations floating together in a sky filled completely with stars,
our hearts will always be one, even when we separate
Thoughts I couldn’t put into words, feelings I wished I could tell you about before,
when they came out of my mouth, I couldn’t help but cry
I didn’t smile up ‘till the end, sorry about that…
Hey my friends, yeah my friends, dear my friends
“My Graduation Toss”, please take it
Hey my friends, yeah my friends
Hey, everybody! Even if I leave,
Yeah, everybody! We’ll still be friends
Dear my friends…I really love you
I’m so glad I was able to meet you all
No matter what kind of memories they may be,
I’ll take every single one away with me, I won’t forget
My present to you right now, “Graduation toss”
I’ve met such wonderful treasures, whenever they light up in my music box,
I’ll always be able to remember that I’ve got friends
If the light that guides us to our destinies points us each to our own separate paths,
then, I'll wipe my tears off and start walking forward
I’ll go past this impulse called “setting off”
Hey my friends, yeah my friends, dear my friends
“My Graduation Toss”, with all my love put into it
Hey my friends, yeah my friends
Oh yeah!