Everyone! An announcement by the Koubaibu.
Good evening everybody!
1.. 2.. We are the Koubaibu!
Finally, this is going to be the very last long Koubaibu MC.
Sorry.
Is there anyone who's glad that it's ending?
Who's glad about the ending of the long MCs by us?
You don't want it to end?
Hai
During the first Koubaibu MC, we had no idea what to say, and just spurted out random MC lines.
Other than that, do you think we have grown?
Thank you very much.
In our final concert, we would like to present the best merchandise to you all.
Therefore, we will now introduce the first item.
And it is:
The 2014 last photo set.
It is the very last photo set of 2014
This picture set consists of the fun development of the graduates, and next year's graduates as they reach for their dream.
Hai
Speaking of which, this is the last time you'll see us in our uniform. Therefore it has a rare kind of feeling.
Here we introduced it, but sorry,
They're all actually sold out.
Sorry!
We apologize!
Sorry.
But you know what,
We have some information for you right now.
Amuse's official online shop called Asmart! will sell the last photo set!
We will sell them!
We can get in trouble for doing this kind of thing without the approval of the teachers.
We'll try our best to persuade the teachers to include this.
So the Fukei-sans who can't buy it today, please look forward to the release at Asmart!
Onegaishimasu
We will now introduce the second item!
And it is:
The Road to Graduation glass!
This glass can be used for special occasions or casual days.
That's right
But you know, glass is fragile, therefore it may break.
They are indeed fragile.
For times like these,
Pre-ordering them is a must.
Say, ShiraSaki, a tragedy happened to you recently right?
Yes, that's right.
Actually,
The other day, I lost my Sakura bus pass case, a Sakura Gakuin merchandise.
Although I'm glad I found it,
I regretted not having a spare in the meantime.
So everybody should also reserve their copy.
To be honest, Yunano would definitely break like 3 or so.
I'm also thinking about buying some for my family.
Maybe like 10 pieces?
That amount sounds about right?
So anyway, please check it out.
Onegaishimasu
There are many more other items,
But the album "Kimi ni Todoke" has these concert exclusive items,
so if you purchase the album from O-east, you will receive a clear file.
To all the ones who haven't purchased it yet, please check it out.
Onegaishimasu
Yes, and also,
Yunano has another merchandise recommendation.
The graduation photo collection, we are going to sell them during this live!
You know, they are autographed
Isn't that great?
We put our hearts into signing them.
So please, everyone, check it out
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
But anyway, forgive me for saying "please check it out, please check it out" over and over.
In the end, for the last bit, we would like to end this with a pose.
There are many other merchandise, so please everyone
Check 'em out!
Everyone, today you will get something from us.
We're going to do a special service for you all!
Please take these autographed T-shirts!
Get ready for us!
Here we go!
We're going to shoot one more!
Thank you so much!
Please buy from us!!!