Farewell address.
It’s still cold but the cherry blossom rows are becoming pink in colour.
The season is coming to begin preparing for spring.
Moa.
Yui.
Hana.
Yunano.
Congratulations on your graduation.
It’s been 5 years since Sakura Gakuin first opened.
So far, we have sent off 9 graduates.
Together with Moa, Yui, Hana, & Yunano, we’ve always sent off the graduates,
so it’s a strange feeling sending you guys off now.
In the 2011 school year, Hana & Rinon were transferred in,
and Moa & Yui became seniors.
I remember the seniors always being kind and gentle and teaching me the choreography.
When it was recording time, I didn’t even know how to sing into the microphone and
you taught me many things right from step 1.
I was in the 5th grade of Elementary school when Hana and I transferred in.
At that time there was no one in the same grade as me, but
Moa and Yui said that it was okay for Moa, Yui, Hana & Rinon to call each other by names only.
So, I was really glad to make some friends in that moment.
In the 2012 school year, Yunano was transferred in.
To me, it was the first time that I had a junior.
With the four of you, the meeting style and timing was different for each of you,
but now, for me, Yunano, Hana, Yui & Moa are all seniors I aspire to be like.
Moa as the Student Council President, always tried her best to unite Sakura Gakuin.
At the lessons every day, some of us would be tired
but you tried to cheer us up and made us smile.
Thanks to that, all the members always smile.
This school year, we ten students had few opportunities to get together
so it took a long time for our ten hearts to become one
but we talked together, laughed and cried a lot.
To Rinon, one by one, it was a very important time.
Yui loves Sakura Gakuin
and decided the setlists for all the concerts.
Yui said she is always thinking about Sakura Gakuin
and didn’t want to think so much about it anymore.
There were a lot of troubles,
thinking about how to make the setlist feel like Sakura Gakuin
and to also have the 2014 school year’s color.
And, Yui would point out our bad points and praise our good points.
If we didn’t improve ourselves, we couldn’t improve together.
When Yui was first transferred in she had a strong “little sister” image,
but the Yui now is almost like Sakura Gakuin’s older sister.
Hana is Rinon’s transfer-in buddy and
looking back to that time, there are many memories.
When you were talking about Pro Wrestling your eyes were sparkling.
The first time we did the Pro Wrestling Circle together,
I was anxious, but within in the severeness there was ease.
Through my experience in the Pro Wrestling Circle
I could learn many various things, so thank you.
And so, as Spirit Chairman, before the concerts and lessons
she lead us in the spirit circle, and actively, our hearts became one.
Hana was always putting in more effort than anyone behind the scenes.
Rinon always saw that in her.
If there was no Sakura Gakuin, I wouldn’t have met Hana
And I’m happy to have transferred in to Sakura Gakuin at the same time as her.
Yunano transferred in a year after Rinon but,
you are older than me by a year.
At first I didn’t know how to approach you
Maybe Yunano had felt the same.
And so, gradually,
without the senior and junior separation, everybody thought about Sakura Gakuin better than before.
When Yunano said that to me, "I feel you are the best person to consult", I was very happy.
She’s the only one out of the 9th graders to have transferred in during Junior High School.
Compared to the other 9th graders, her time in Sakura Gakuin was shorter but
she put more effort in and went through more troubles than the others.
I've known that for a long time.
I think it’s really amazing.
Each of the four have their own charms.
I have learned many things from them.
You’ve been watching over us but
this year’s 9th graders have been worrying about various things alone
so we’ve been wondering if you’ve been okay
However, even when the four of them are doing extra-curricular activities
we thought it was really difficult for us,
they set an example for us juniors, and you did your very best in everything
“Even though we’re separated, our hearts are one.”
There are so many things this year’s four graduates taught us but,
I think this one is the best.
Rinon has recently often thought
there’s nothing sad about Sakura Gakuin graduations.
Graduation is necessary in order to become a Super Lady.
I would be lying if I said that we won't get lonely,
but today, to the four people graduating from Sakura Gakuin
I want you to try your best in achieving your dreams.
I don’t know how us juniors will handle being entrusted with everything but
what the graduates have built up for us until now
will continue to be an important part of Sakura Gakuin.
We’ll also create a new history for Sakura Gakuin next year.
Even though you’re graduating please watch over us.
I've not expressed my gratitude in lots of words but
We all think we can't thank you more,
more than we can express in words
Moa.
Yui.
Hana.
Yunano.
Congratulations on your graduation.
And, thank you.
March 29th, 2015
Current Student Representative.
2nd grade in Junior High, Isono Rinon.