Start! Let's set out running at our very limit
Jump! We won't lose to anyone
Then let's chase each of our dreams and shine like we're second to none
Dream! Outside the classroom window
Chance! There's an infinitely expanding future
So fall in love, dream your dreams, let your own flowers bloom
Let the buds bloom, let the sakura bloom
in this garden of learning, My school days
The rhythm which pulsed through the ground becomes wind;
Surely that is where dreams set off running
Our desire is a beginning: to gently foster a feeling
which overflows, even if suppressed. We await the time when the flowers open
Ah, Sakura Gakuin!
Start! A gesture from you, my beloved
Smile! That passing profile
I look quietly during class, and wish that my imagination can reach you
Wish! Those precious words
Say! How I wish for you to say them!
To not give up on anyone; how are you to act rightly?
Let the buds bloom, let the sakura bloom
in this garden of my heart, My sweet days
Start! Let's set out running at our very limit; we won't lose to anyone
Then let's chase each of our dreams and shine like we're second to none
Believe! Outside the classroom window
Chance! There's an infinitely expanding future
So fall in love, dream your dreams, let your own flowers bloom
Let the buds bloom, let the sakura bloom
in this garden of learning, My school days