Walking out, the road spreads in front of my eyes
It’s my first step closer to adulthood
My departure day
Today’s bright blue sky is more dazzling than usual, isn’t it?
as if it’s congratulating everyone who is moving on
It’d be scary if I were all alone, but my friends are here with me
The precious time that we spent together is our bond, huh?
Even if I’m going away,
we got to know each other, our hearts are one
I’m not on my own
Looking up at the sky, nobody knows what it holds yet
Hey, a shining tomorrow is surely waiting for us
That’s why I won’t cry! Today is only the beginning
A bunch of smiles are gathered together under the sakura for
my departure day
Which path should I travel? I was troubled by that, so
We were always staying behind after school, consulting with each other
If the future is uncertain, I’ll just be honest with my own dreams
That’s my answer, so, I’ll be alright, okay?
To tell you the truth, I’m somewhat sad, but
in the print club photo I’m texting you, I’m smiling through my tears,
making a double-peace sign like I always do
Thank you, I’m so glad we became friends
We cried, sulked, and smiled together
Because of that, I have faith that this “farewell” is only the beginning, don’t you think?
Until the day when our dreams come true and we meet again, this is
my departure day
I won’t forget
meeting here
We overcame even the painful stuff together, so
inside our hearts, let’s make a promise:
You and I are friends!
That’s right, even we’re grown up, we’ll be friends forever, won’t we…
Looking up at the sky, nobody knows what it holds yet
Hey, a shining tomorrow is surely waiting for us
That’s why I won’t cry! Today is only the beginning
A bunch of smiles are gathered together under the sakura for
my departure day
Thank you, I’m so glad we became friends
We cried, sulked, and smiled together
Because of that, I have faith that this “farewell” is only the beginning, don’t you think?
Until the day when our dreams come true and we meet once more,
See you again...