Finally, the day has come here at the overcrowded NHK Hall!
The grand final of the SKGP tournament between Taguchi Hana and Isono Rinon of the Pro-wrestling Circle.
It's the last match between them, realised at this graduation show.
Let's recollect the history of their battles... the first match was fought at the opening show of the SKGP on 27/09
Announcer:
Kiyono Shigeki
And the 2nd round was fought at EX-theater in Roppongi
There was an unbelievable incursion by Yamaide Aiko!
And the 3rd and final match is going to be fought here and now, at NHK Hall!
At last, the first champion of the SKGP will be determined!
Look at the stage! The two competitors who are about to have a championship match for the SKGP now appear!
They show us grim faces with their lips closed tightly.
First, Isono Rinon, the representative of the remaining students.
Is she going to win against her master, to say a requiem for the Taguchi-era?
And the opponent is Taguchi Hana, who want's to show off her superiority as a senpai. Is she going to get the graduation certificate named Champion Belt by herself?
The gong to start the match....is struck!
Hey! Here you come into the ring again...do you know anything about Pro-wrestling?
Today is the last day of your dominance
Taguchi-san, thank you for your good work.
I must tell you one thing. The Champion Belt of SKGP is still out of your league
If you want to get it, you must go beyond yourself
Hey, you guys! Make some noise!
The winner is... Taguchi Hana!
For Isono Rinon... the SKGP Belt is still out of reach
Now Taguchi Hana has her graduation certificate,
The glorious Champion Belt of the SKGP!
Oh, look! Taguchi now holds a mic! What is she going to say?
Hey, Rinon
Hana can't hold this belt
You know what I mean?