Shaking heart! Stand up, it’s now or never
The time has come to test our strength
Come, let our clashing souls
send sparks flying
Burning! If you feel your heart beat…it’s getting across
Inside the blowing wind, all alone
I fight against it and keep going—these two hands of mine
aren’t here to hurt others
They should be used to help someone else
Spin them, make it gloriously brilliant
Spin, like a windmill
Spinning Heart! Break out running! It’s now or never
A signal that tests your heart
Come, the overflowing earnestness
Will scatter tears
Ready! I’ll deliver this message until my voice grows hoarse
Shaking heart! Stand up, it’s now or never
The time has come to test our strength
Come, let our clashing souls
send sparks flying
Burning! If you feel your heart beat…it’s getting across