An angel with white wings on her back
A black devil with a spiky tail
Perched on top of my left and right shoulder,
these two are on at full blast
Once you take the first step, there’s no going back
Even if you turn around, there won’t be a path there anymore
Perched on top of my left and right shoulder,
the same voices as always are on at full blast
“Let’s just lay low, that way we won’t regret it”
the devil beckons
“Gather your courage, be strong”
the angel whispers, dabadouda
Once again, I’m kept up at night
Magic spells and prayers, spiritual
I have a long consultation over the phone with an astrologist
Perched on top of my left and right shoulder,
the voices I’ve gotten used to hearing are on at full blast
the same voices as always are on at full blast
“Let’s attack strong,	it’s so simple”
the devil beckons
“Let’s be good girls now, don’t risk it”
the angel whispers, dabadouda
Once again, I’m kept up at night
“Let’s just lay low, that way we won’t regret it”
the devil beckons
“Gather your courage, be strong”
the angel whispers, dabadouda
Their two voices
“Let’s attack strong,	it’s so simple”
“Let’s be good girls now, don’t risk it”
This is my way dabadouda
I’ve made up my mind
Angel and devil, goodbye, the both of you