Hello! IVY
Let's go for a cool look
Cooler, cooler, cooler
IVY! IVY! IVY Girl!
With clean scented straight hair
Hello! IVY IVY IVY Girl! Yeah!!
As the sunset dyes the school orange
I notice you swaying the swing back and forth
with nobody on it
What's wrong?
Don't worry here all alone
Let's walk together while you
tell me what's on your mind right now
In the future you'll be
The sweet IVY girl
The shining IVY girl
The kind IVY girl
The brilliantly sparkling IVY girl
Let's go for a fresh look
Fresher, fresher, fresher
IVY! IVY! IVY Girl!
Polish your fashion sense up
Hello! IVY IVY IVY Girl! Yeah!!
Let's go for a cute look
Cuter, cuter, cuter
IVY! IVY! IVY Girl
Trad is the coolest look
Hello! IVY IVY IVY Girl! Yeah!!
Hello! IVY IVY Yeah!!
IVY Girl!
Hello! IVY! IVY! IVY!
Hello! IVY! IVY! IVY Girl! Yeah!!