Fry the fluffy rice, *rat-a-tat*
Chicken rice with a percussion beat
The broccoli’s maracas, the tomato’s castanets
A salad instrumental band
A delicious harmony, there’s a racket in the kitchen
A tiny musical note: cherry blossom cheese
When you line them up, they form a wonderful melody
It’s the ultimate rice omelette
Ah! The recipe is my heart
Eat up, it’s paradise
My inspiration is your smile
The basil sauce on top of the fluffy eggs
Is a string section, playing
How about some ham, cut in the shape of cherry blossoms     Tum-tum♪Ta-tum♪
A spring scenery tambourine
Is the sound of everyone’s low, rumbling stomach the bassist?
Hold on, piano! The salted cherry blossoms play, *plunk-plunk*
Strumming along to this miraculous music collaboration
The perfect rice omelette
Oh! I can hear the cheers
Hey, this will surely set a precedent
My aim is a Western-style restaurant
A delicious melody♪
It’s the ultimate rice omelette
Ah! The recipe is my heart
Eat up, it’s paradise
My inspiration is your smile
The perfect rice omelette
Oh! I can hear the cheers
Yes♪ Surely with a full stomach
We’ll encounter lots of fun stuff
I'm Aiko
I'm Momoko
I'm Marin
We are Sakura Gakuin Cooking Club, Mini Pati!
Thank you for the meal!
Bye Bye, thanks for the meal, bye bye.