Everyone! This is an announcement from the Purchasing Club!
Good evening to everyone!
Good evening!
Ready, set...
We are the Purchasing Club!
Nice to meet you!
Well then, without delay I'd like to introduce the new goods.
The first item is... here it is!
A glass!
Yes!
All right, this glass can be an item for everyday use
Besides that, you can also purchase it as a memento for today's graduation ceremony
And then what else... also, using this item you can toast the member's birthday, right?
Everyone, don't you do that?
You do, right?
Oh, I'm glad!
Therefore, everyone please by all means get this glass!
Also, it might happen that it breaks, so please buy at least three in advance!
Three! Did you hear that? Even those who are sitting at the third floor? It's three!
Good!
All right! Thank you very much!
And now, next item...
The next item... is this!
The last photo set!
Yes! In this last photo set, the members graduating from elementary school Maaya and Marin,
and those who are graduating from middle school and Sakura Gakuin, the three 3rd year members
There's solo shots of these five graduating members, and this set has also the very last group shot for this school year's members.
Therefore I'd really like everyone to buy this photo set, but...
actually this is... sold out! I'm sorry! We're sorry!
But, after the graduation ceremony is over, we can quickly run to the staff room teachers
and for this, at Amuse official homep... nay it's not homepage... I mean, at Amuse online shop
at ASmart, we can try and ask them so that it can be bought,
So together with the fukei san, us members of the Purchasing Club can ask for this, ok?
Please!
Thank you very much!
At the live viewing venue, there's still some goods left over, it might be just a little bit, but there might still be some left,
So please everyone, check it out!
Everyone, it's year's end sale, here we go! Here it comes!
One more shot, let's go!
Here it comes!
Last one! Here we go!
Thank you very much!
Please buy from us!!!