And now, we will be addressed by Sakura Gakuin Principal Kuramoto Mitsuru
Well, it has become Sakura season.
When the Sakura bloom, it is time for Sakura Gakuin's graduation ceremony.
The Sakura bloomed about five days early this year.
But even if the Sakura bloom started, it doesn't feel like it's getting warmer.
The Sakura are not really blooming, with only a few just starting to bloom.
Like those flowers, it feels like you are graduating too early
Everyone probably feels the same way.
There's a lot to think about.
The three graduating this year don't lose to their seniors at all in being interesting.
I mean, Shirai Saki was a Fukei!
She is a fan of Sakura Gakuin.
A Fukei became a member of Sakura Gakuin
That was a miracle for her, I suppose.
Her dream came true at her age!
I worried how someone would be motivated after getting her dream.
She had to overcome such a special situation.
There was surely a type of pressure that only Shirai would understand.
She overcame that and did really well as the Talk Chairperson. Thank you very much.
About the timing for when Ooga Saki transferred in...
It was right after the 1st class graduated.
Because the 1st class had been the cardinal members of Sakura Gakuin,
we worried about what would happen to Sakura Gakuin after they left.
We were nervous and tried different things.
Surrounded in that environment, not even knowing left from right...
I think you were tested in many different ways.
I feel like you went along even though I didn't know which way to go.
You have a lot of guts.
Even though I think you worried about many things,
I feel like you gritted your teeth and overcame.
Thank you!
And then Isono Rinon...
You are the only one in all of Sakura Gakuin, the ONLY one,
who has experienced everything from since Sakura Gakuin became a school until now. The only one.
You were there even during my first nightmare class.
You had a terrible experience, really.
You were just sitting there spacing out. "Is she okay?!"
I thought, "Is she alive?!"
I also thought, "Is she a living thing"
Since then, you have experienced everything
and I was worried about having you become the Student Council president.
But we decided to let you do it
and after just one year, it is surprising how much you've grown.
You really got yourself together!
What was that speech just now?
Without making many mistakes,
Isn't that great?
Such a long speech.
Even the content of the speech,
I don't know how other idols do it, but they write these themselves!
That's the type of thing that makes me believe Sakura Gakuin is raising Super Ladies.
I heard you want to be a theater director after you graduate.
That is wonderful.
I wonder, how did you become so mature?
You want to become Super by supporting others. I think that is great!
Please debut by working with Sakura Gakuin.
After about 5 years?
Right?
Sakura Gakuin is indeed a school.
A school to help people become Super.
You will all graduate, whatever path you choose
Isono wants to be a director
and I think you two should continue thinking about your future,
I think no matter which genre you go to
that those who have graduated from Sakura Gakuin
will be looked at as Super people.
I believe you will be the center of happiness for many people.
It's fine, without a doubt!
All of the former graduates are now gonna be that.
So believe in yourself and have confidence.
And fry ... uh I mean fly to the future! In the end, I made a mistake!
I lost to Isono!
Congratulations!