We will begin the graduation ceremony
for Sakura Gakuin class of 2015.
And now, the current students.
Continuing, the graduating students.
Please bow.
Please take your seats.
And now, Principal Kuramoto Mitsuru
will present the graduation certificates.
Elementary 6th Year, Asou Maya
Yes!
Graduation Certificate, Ms. Asou Maya.
As of today, we certify that you have completed the acquisition
of dance and song skills required to graduate elementary Sakura Gakuin.
Heisei 28, March. Sakura Gakuin Principal Kuramoto Mitsuru.
Congratulations!
Elementary 6th Year, Hidaka Marin.
Yes!
Graduation Certificate, Ms. Hidaka Marin.
The same as previously stated.
Congratulations!
Continuing, the middle school graduates.
Middle 3rd Year, Isono Rinon.
Yes!
Graduation Certificate, Ms. Isono Rinon
As of today, we certify that you have completed the acquisition
of all skills required to complete all Sakura Gakuin activities.
We certify that you have taken your first steps to becoming a Super Lady.
Heisei 28, March. Sakura Gakuin Principal Kuramoto Mitsuru.
Please...
Congratulations!
Middle 3rd Year, Ooga Saki.
Yes!
Graduation Certificate, Ms. Ooga Saki.
The same as previously stated.
Please...
Congratulations!
Middle 3rd Year, Ms. Shirai Saki.
Yes!
Graduation Certificate, Ms. Shirai Saki.
The same as previously stated.
Congratulations!