We gallop towards the classroom, at that moment, my heart throbs
It’s the first day back from our holiday break,
when I looked up just a little, you suddenly looked grown up
My cellphone is full of pictures of us goofing around together
Even the awful bangs that I had back then
that were cut too short are now a fond memory
Try as I might (try as I might) to act like an adult
My knees still (knees still) hurt
I wish I could immediately grow as tall as I stretch,
But just watch, someday I'll catch up
My bangs have grown back out just a little bit
but I haven't grown nearly enough height-wise
And now I'm beginning to understand the mysterious ache inside my chest that used to puzzle me
I wonder if I've grown up a little more than back then in some respects?
The small bud in me was showered in sunlight and burst into light
Getting closer (getting closer) and being left further behind
Getting closer (getting closer) I go on trying to overtake you
The sun I was able to see when I stretched out as far as I could is somehow so big,
It feels that with just a little bit more, I'll be able to reach it
Everyone, please clap your hands together with us!
On me!
Fall in!
One, two, three!
Gymnastics formation, spread out!
About, face!
One, two, three!
Right, face!
One, two!
A little more than today (more than today) and a little more than tomorrow, forever...
I'll (I'll) grow up for sure...
Try as I might (try as I might) to act like an adult
My knees still (knees still) hurt
I wish I could immediately grow as tall as I stretch,
But just watch, someday I'll definitely catch up