What is the probability of the miracle that I encountered you
Tell me of my destiny, number magic
One, ten, One hundred, a thousand, ten thousand, a hundred million, a trillion, ten quadrillion
Let’s dream a big dream together!
If you should wish to know the area of a circle
It’s the radius times the radius times pi
Its circumference is the diameter times pi
If you use these formulas you’ll understand quickly
Body weight, sleep, calorie measurements
These beautiful secrets are entirely arithmetic
The Beauty Looking Back and Venus de Milo
With angles and ratios their cuteness goes up!
The establishment of the miracle of having encountered you
Fulfills my destiny, number magic
One, ten, One hundred, a thousand, ten thousand, a hundred million, a trillion, ten quadrillion
But I still have many dreams!
If you’re after the volume of a cylinder or prism
It’s base area times the height; it’s surprisingly simple
A pointed hat, which would be a pyramid or a cone
Is just that amount divided by three, which you ought to understand quickly
Tailoring, cooking, and even confectionery
Provided it’s housework, the basis of any of these is arithmetic
Count the thread-gaps, measure the sugar
Come up with a figure and your feminine power goes up and becomes your ally!
What is the probability of the miracle that I encountered you
I wish to know my destiny, number magic
How many tenths or hundredths or thousandths or ten-thousandths,
Such happiness is there, that I want to embrace you!
What is the probability of the miracle that I encountered you
Tell me of my destiny, number magic
One, ten, One hundred, a thousand, ten thousand, a hundred million, a trillion, ten quadrillion
Together, a big dream –
Still, many dreams –
Let’s dream this exciting dream!