Good evening everyone!
Good evening!
We are the unit limited to the period of growth, Sakura Gakuin!
Nice to meet you!
Well, at last this day has come.
Yes!
The Road to Graduation 2015...
ready, set...
Final!
Yeah!
Ah... today it's the final...
I see really a lot of people wearing suits, really... amazing!
Amazing, isn't it. Thank you very much. Thank you!
I can see you perfectly!
Yes.
I feel that the ratio of suits is increasing
That's right
The level of awareness is pretty high...
Yes! Thank you very much!
Then, please let us briefly introduce ourselves.
Starting from Momoko.
All right, I'm Okazaki Momoko, 1st year of middle school
I'm Yoshida Soyoka, 5th grader of elementary school
I'm Yamaide Aiko, 1st year of middle school
I'm Fujihira Kano, 5th grader of elementary school
I'm Okada Megumi, 1st year of middle school
I'm Hidaka Marin, 6th grader of elementary school [nice to meet...]
I'm Kurashima Sara, 2nd year of middle school
I'm Asou Maaya, 6th grader of elementary school
I'm Kurosawa Mirena, 2nd year of middle school
I'm Education Chairman Ooga Saki, 3rd year of middle school
I'm Student Council President Isono Rinon, 3rd year of middle school
I'm Talk Chairman Shirai Saki, 3rd year of middle school
That's all. Today as well, with these 12 members, we are growing and full of energy. Please treat us kindly.
All right. Wow... at last, the day has come.
Yeah, exactly.
It was quick... yes, it was.
Yes. But talking about this live show,
It's amazing... together with last year's graduation ceremony,
and the event held in December during this school year,
which was the live show for the 5th anniversary, following these events,
this live show will be broadcast live in movie theaters throughout the country!
Yeeahh!
Thank you very much. We're truly happy for this.
Kanagawa Kenmin Hall is such a big venue,
and there's lots of fukei-san here, but
there's also the live viewing, being watched by so many fukei-san
I feel a bit nervous, but I'm also happy.
Exactly. That's right.
Now... Oh, I'm sorry I'm sorry...
It's OK.
What's the matter? What happened?
It's OK, it's OK.
OK? It's all right.
The thing that just happened here, I've hit Soyo's mic by mistake
Thinking that this will show at the movie theatre too...
Isn't that a weird feeling?
Right, that's weird.
Truly that's amazing.
It feels like we are in the same place together with the fukei from all over Japan.
I'm really happy for this.
Yes. Thank you very much!
Those people who came to see Sakura Gakuin
for the first time might be a little surprised,
but in Sakura Gakuin, the moment you graduate from middle school, you must also graduate from the group.
That's an iron-bound rule, therefore today we three
3rd year members will graduate from the group.
Yes.
So, what are the feelings of these three members right now?
Honestly speaking, I don't have a real feeling of this at all...
Huh?
Even if I'm asked about my feelings now...
That's right!
For me too... before I was standing on this stage
I didn't have a real feeling of this at all
But once I was standing here on stage, like every
year when I see all the fukei-san wearing suits
I think, this year the moment has come again.
Yes, this is what happens, really.
Time goes fast!
Well, anyway today I'd like to achieve "perfect combustion"
All right! I'll do my best!
So that we won't lose to them, the current students will give their best too!
Yes! We'll give our best!
With this spirit, today really all the members are motivated.
Yes!
You're all fired up as well, aren't you?
OK.
Thank you very much. Impressive.
Everyone is motivated, so... I'd like to hear your voices more!
Yes!
First, everyone sitting on the 2nd and 3rd floors!
Are you ready to enjoy the show?
Thank you very much!
That's nice.
Then, next... everyone sitting on the 1st floor
You can still let us hear your voice more!
Amazing!
All right. Thank you very much.
And then also... did I catch you off guard?
All the watchers of the Live Viewing!
More, more!
Won't you get into this excited mood even more?
Yeeahh!
We could hear you! That was perfect!
Thank you very much!
Then, last...
Fukei-san from all over Japan,
More, more, more! Are you ready to enjoy the show?