Omelette rice was delicious!
Wasn't it? That was cute.
That was a delicious meal.
Thanks for the meal. We actually didn't have any, though...
All right. We had the privilege of showing here our club activities.
Everyone, did you like it?
Oh, thank you very much!
All right! First of all, the Purchasing Club
Yeah.
This year too, they used the bazooka during the interlude...
Yes.
Then the Go Home Club, In the interlude they did the word association while doing leapfrogs
We challenged ourselves to do new things.
Exactly.
Yes. Well, these were our club activities this year.
Here I think, talking about this year, we could try and review some past events a bit.
Everyone, aren't you curious to hear a bit of inside information about us?
Oohh. Good.
All right. So...
I think we could ask everyone to tell some inside stories about our music videos.
To begin with, are there some about the music video of Mathematica?
Yes! Yes! Yes!
Then...
Saki chan!
Yes!
I'm sorry.
Well...
During the intro part of Mathematica,
There was a scene where we ate sweets.
Yeah.
Er... Mirena said 'soon is the time for snacks'
That time, we ate sweets together
2015 nendo had just started, so it was the first experience for the transfer students.
They were really happy to eat such things during the filming.
Yeah, that's right.
Basically, we are eating in many videos this year, right?
Like in Kirameki no Kakera... yes, we eat several things.
That's true.
But then we were also anxious about the staff room teachers...
Exactly.
Just a little bit, when the teachers were absent
We stealthily ate things...
Yes, we did.
Wait... the staff teachers can hear this.
Well you know... for us three that's irrelevant right now!
That's nasty!
You are revealing too much!
Hey!
That's so mean!
Stop, we'll really get in trouble!
In the future, I feel there won't be eating scenes anymore.
Oh no!
Really...
Yes.
Well, that was it.
Then next, is there anything from Kirameki no Kakera or School Days videos?
Did anything leave an impression?
Hmm...
Sara?
When we did the filming for Kirameki no Kakera,
We went to the seaside.
And the sand entered inside our shoes really a lot.
Yes...
And it didn't go away
Exactly
That left a strong impression.
And that time...
after that, even at LoGiRL
All the time the sand from the beach kept coming from our shoes.
That's true!
With that clink clink sound.
Exactly!
So in a way this sand...
is a memory, like Kirameki no Kakera [shards of glitter]
I'm sorry. Wait a minute please.
That's right.
Wait a minute! It's sand, a fairly amount of sand.
Y
Right.
And I thought I said a good one
It was, a little bit. A little. You tried to show off.
Well then
We have all these memories, but
talking about our activities...
We appear every week at a regular program,
we make a live broadcast at LoGiRL...
Are there any inside stories about LoGiRL?
Oh. Rinon chan.
Yes, it's about the recent final episode
During the last episode for this school year,
All 12 members appeared on LoGiRL
Yes.
About Mori Sensei...
the plan was making him eat a huge quantity of sushi with wasabi inside
Yes.
But eventually
us three as well, the 3rd year members
like, we were intrigued...
You ate it.
Yes we ate it.
And then...
There was really an extraordinary amount of wasabi
Yes! Furthermore, the color of the wasabi was yellow
Exactly.
We thought it was just wasabi,
But it was together with grated daikon radish, chili pepper and mustard,
like, there was everything mixed in that
Yes.
It was terrible, really...
Such quantity of wasabi...
Ah!
Welcome back!
Sorry for interrupting...
Don't worry, it's fine.
I don't think I've ever eaten such quantity of wasabi at once.
Probably.
But after that, Mori Sensei
Since it was the last one for that school year...
You know?
He bought ice cream for us!
We ate it right?
Yes we did.
What about that? Yamaide Ice san
What about that? That's her new name.
It was really good, and also...
Er... saying it was more than they could eat,
someone gave me more.
Megu gave it to Aiko!
Kano gave some too!
I wanted to eat it, but I gave it to you.
You got a lot! Quite a bit!
But wasn't Aiko on ice cream restriction?
Yes, when we did the live show in February
she said, Ice Dazs ice...
but asking the staff room teachers, it seems
that she had stopped eating Dazs ice cream in February too.
Soyo saw it!
Aiko chan! Soyo says she saw it too!
Before that, she ate ice cream together with Megu.
We ate strawberry gelato together, didn't we.
Yes we saw it!
You know... if you all talk together, they can't hear what you say!
Really, I can't understand.
We wanted to talk a bit too much.
OK. To summarize, Aiko gave up eating Dazs ice cream.
That's right.
I'm sorry.
Well, we also have lots of memories about such trivial things.
Surely, also together with the fukei san,
Having fun together at live shows and events,
I think during this year we made a lot of memories together with the fukei.
Yes. We are truly grateful for that.
Thank you very much.
All right.
Yes. But still the live show goes on.
After this, I'd like to proceed to the next song,
Then, the next song. Marin, please introduce it.
Yes. All right, for the next song
together with the fukei san,
I'd like to get lost in a mysterious land.
Please listen to... Sleep Wonder!