Thank you very much!
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Well, there really aren't many opportunities for us 3rd year members to remain alone.
Surely, the 3rd year members alone in such a big stage...
It was only at the graduation ceremony.
'Was'... you say?
Oops, I said it in the past.
But... we third year members
Despite appearances, we joined the group in different school years
I joined the group in 2013 nendo
[* changes from informal to formal]
I joined in 2012 nendo
I joined the group in 2011 nendo.
For me they are senpai, even though we are of the same age.
At first, really...
We weren't that close
Yes.
It's not that we were on bad terms!
Of course not.
But honestly, we weren't close either.
That's true...
The fact that we didn't talk much might sound a bit exaggerated
But honestly speaking, before this nendo
Absolutely...
We didn't talk almost at all.
That's right.
Despite the fact that we were of the same age
I would have never expected it would end like this
Yes.
But...
Surely, once we were 3rd year members
I feel we could strengthen our bond.
Exactly.
That's right. What's more, we three...
Recently, at a school trip,
Actually, we went to a trip for a photo album.
And we really had a lot of fun!
This kind of atmosphere between us started to come out
I thought "Why didn't we get along earlier!"
Yes, it's really unique.
In 2nd year, if we could have met our future selves
Wouldn't we be really surprised?
That's right.
But in a way...
Now that I come to think of it...
I guess we're the most intimate among the 3rd year members up to now.
We have self-confidence. Indeed. I'm confident.
All right.
This song we three sing...
Actually...
It's included in the album released on the 3rd of March...
Today,  I'd like to introduce this song that we 3rd year members sing.
Yes!
This song is really packed with Sakura Gakuin's daily life, therefore
Everyone, by all means, please pay attention to the lyrics.
Then, please listen to...
Michi Shirube