Thank you very much!
A moment ago, the 3rd year members performed Michi Shirube
Yes.
I think the enrolled students would like to tell their impressions about it now.
Anyone?
Yes! Yes!
Megu!
Hooray!
Yes. Well Megu...
Well, the 3rd year members...
Their expression while singing...
How was it again? "A cherry blossom which heads for the future at the front line"
Watching that part from the back
There... you can see them right? Watching their expression there
Yeah.
Their expressions during that part looked really dignified...
With this kind of "let's go towards the future" kind of feeling, it was very cool.
I would never have thought we would be praised like that.
Thank you.
I feel embarrassed.
I'm happy for that. I'm glad.
OK. Next.
Here! Here!
I have no choice... Mirena!
Yes!
Finally... I won!
I was waiting for this occasion.
Were you?
Yes.
In the part where they sing "We wrote on looseleaf an unfinished tale"
Er...
I liked it even by listening to the song alone
But looking it together with the choreo, really, really...
I was almost about to cry
I think I will never forget about this.
Seriously.
Loose-leaf, you know...
Gives the image of our blog, our school diary
Exactly.
If you were really moved by that, I'd like you to write more diaries in the future!
That's right!
We were told that! We were told until the very end!
I think writing at a pace of one per week is a good performance.
Certainly! We'll give our best.
OK, then.
Should we hear another?
Sara chaan! OK, then Soyo.
Hooray!
Er... for Soyo it's about the singing of Saki chan
I like the 'i' in "donna tonneru mo nukereba kitto"
Do you like the 'i'?
I like the way she sings the 'i'
I'd like you to sing it once...
I'd like to listen! Yes, I'd like it.
I'd like to hear it.
The fukei san too
Everyone, you'd like to listen don't you?
See!
??????????
That's right. Exactly.
No matter which tunnel we will come out from, for sure...
The 'i' you sang right now.
She's good!
Was the 'i' I sang right now OK?
This was better than in the rehearsal.
Exactly.
It was good that she kept asking you to sing that many times.
Today she got a perfect score.
??????????
Thank you!
That was nice. That's good.
So, Soyo gave this Michi Shirube a perfect score
The fukei san, too... did you listen properly to our feelings?
Thank you very much.
Also, everyone at the live viewing!
Did you carefully listen to the singing of Saki chan pointed out by Soyo?
Yes, did you listen?
They did.
Thank you very much. That's good. Yeah.
????????
Sorry, sorry.
Well, the 3rd year members have performed this song Michi Shirube
Now we are approaching the second part of the graduation ceremony
That's right.
Every year, at the graduation ceremony
There's Sakura Gakuin songs in the graduation season that are passed on from year to year.
Exactly.
After this... we'd like to perform one of these graduation songs
Yes.
That graduation song from 2012 nendo...
I'd like to introduce it now.
Yes!
Then, please listen!