Thank you very much
Lastly... ah-
We reached the end, so...
The remaining members will share their thoughts with the graduating members
Okay
You three have nicely overseen Sakura Gakuin this year
No matter how the members change
Our bonds will never change
The spirit of Sakura Gakuin will never change
I understand that
Everyone understands that
So please keep on watching over us
Thank you so much for today!
Okay
Rinon-chan, Saki-chan, C-chan. Congratulations on graduating.
Erm... Soyo... Isn't really good at sit-ups
Isn't she too cheerful?
While dancing... Erm...
I might be a hindrance in dancing
Becomi- ah, did I say something wrong?
She said the word 'hindrance'??
Well, I'll work even harder after becoming a 6th grader
You spoke right
So keep supporting us, ok?
Let's hang out again
Thank you so much for today!
We'll hang out
Yeah
Yeah we will
Well, I'm really grateful...
to the three seniors
Rinon-chan, Saki-chan, C-chan
Thank you so much
While dancing, or singing... and when I had troubles... thank you for hugging me
I want you to keep hugging me even after today
So cute!
Truly, thank you for everything!
Okay
Up until today, during this one year, you three taught me a lot of things
You were so friendly towards me, and sometimes angry, too
And we also cried together at times
Personally...
The times we spent together with you...
I will treasure them forever...
Thank you so much!
I think the fact that this Sara is standing here is thanks to you three
I can't thank you enough
Well...
When I thought I wasn't ready to be a senior
You told me "You can't change if you don't try changing by yourself"
Really...
In my heart...
I will work hard next year while cherishing those words.
Thank you so much
C-chan, Saki-chan, Rinon-chan! Congratulations on graduating.
I spent three years together with you three seniors, in Sakura Gakuin
In these three years, we made a lot of different memories...
fun memories, and even sad, or painful ones
But now, I think, they are all great memories
Without forgetting those memories,
I'll work hard in Sakura Gakuin until my senior year
So please keep watching over us!
Thank you!
Okay, first of all
C-chan, Saki-chan, Rinon-chan, congratulations on graduating!
These three seniors praised me a lot,
were angry at me a lot, and I learned a lot from them.
But really, I received great education from them
Even after they graduate, we will keep up the traditions of Sakura Gakuin
So please be at ease and work hard to become Super Ladies
Thank you so much!
Rinon-chan, Saki-chan, C-chan
Congra- eh?
Congratulations on graduating
Well...
C-chan...
I didn't really like talking and was bad at it too
:(
taught me a lot...
You can do it!
I came to love talking
Next, C- Rinon-chan
Rinon-chan, Rinon-chan
When we first met, she was so tall
More than just her height
Her heart was big too, I was really surprised
At my first show I lifted up Rinon-chan
And I want to hug her at our last show together too
Woah!
May I?
Great!
Woah!
Amazing
Please keep supporting us
Lastly, Saki-chan
At our first lesson when I started crying
you were the first to come to comfort me
Thank you
That makes me feel good.
Please keep being my big sister
Thank you very much!
Well, first of all
Rinon-chan, Saki-chan, C-chan, congratulations on graduating.
I'm here. It's my turn.
I'm doing my best here
Well I just thought your pro-ness is still strong
I couldn't help laughing
Momoko: Her pro-ness is still strong at the end
C-chan: "First of all"
Laughing?... hrmph...
Okay.
I transferred into the 2nd grade of Jr. High this year
Since I transferred into that higher grade
I couldn't really dance and wasn't confident in my singing
I was incredibly depressed one time
At that time
Everyone... the seniors encouraged me
They supported me, always cheered me up
If they didn't...
The Mirena you see now wouldn't be here
So from now on, you guys will step onto the road of a Super Lady
I will always support that dream of yours
Next year, along with Sara, I will become a senior
I would like to become a senior like you three were this year
Thank you for everything!
Well, we'd like to say some words too
Okay
Well, with this ceremony...
we won't be able to meet much with the Fukei any more
And with you guys, too
We met every day...
Those times are coming to an end
It's a very lonely feeling
But
But I...
Next year...
I believe that you'll work hard next year
I'm expecting a lot from you
So...
I will...
I will keep supporting you together with the Fukei next nendo
So please do your best!
Yes!
I'm truly grateful for the Fukei who kept supporting us this year
Lastly, I want to say one more thing
Sakura Gakuin will live on forever!
Thank you very much!
Okay!
In the 2015 nendo
I was really nervous greeting the transfer-ins
But...
Right now, I'm incredibly grateful I could experience the 2015 nendo of Sakura Gakuin
That's because...
When something happened to us seniors, you were always full of smiles
So... even if something was going on with the seniors
Without change... you called me "Saki-chan", or "Education Chairman"
I was really happy
You always gave me more energy or courage
I'm really thankful for that
Really... but...
They were very honest
Very, very honest
They always told me their feeling directly
There were times I was even surprised by that
But in that way, directly in front of us,
seeing you come to us that directly...
Thanks to that, I was able to be open with my feelings too
Well... before, Mori-sensei said "The seniors were able to make this kind of atmosphere"
But in the end... maybe that was the case, but...
I truly think it's all thanks to you
Also
Being able to continue my activities in Sakura Gakuin
was all thanks to the fukei. You helped me out a lot of times
I can't thank you enough
But I want to say thank you.
I'm truly thankful to you!
And lastly, please let me do this once
Make all those flowers of hope... bloom!
AAAAND!
GOOD!
OOGANING!
Thank you very much!
Amazing!
So many Ooganing circles
They're really in sync, aren't they?
Amazing
Thank you so much!
Okay
With this, I'd like to brag a little bit
I felt like I was going to cry
But I still haven't
Great!
This will remain Sakura Gakuin history
It will
Amazing, right?
Splendid
Okay
I spent five years in Sakura Gakuin
Looking back, there were painful times
and I have a lot of regrets
But I have a lot more happy memories
Meeting different people, experiencing different things,
performing on a lot of stages in these five years
Seeing the many faces of the Fukei, having the loving staff around us,
my dream of becoming a stage director was born
Truth be told, I'm kind of anxious now
Obviously I'm nervous about stepping into a new world
But I want to try out more things I'm bad at, or haven't tried yet
I want to become confident in being able to reach that dream
I'll work hard to be able to come back here as a stage director for Sakura Gakuin
And I want to do something too
I AM?
RINON!
Thank you very much!
Please keep supporting Sakura Gakuin and us too!
Thank you for coming here today!
Thank you very much!
We are Sakura Gakuin!
Bye bye!
Thank you very much!
English Subtitle by FukeiSubs