Ooga!
Please look forward to her self-introduction which changes so often
Will you look down on us? Or upward?
In this year...I'll go from above!
Isono!
Born on the 'Genius star' but she is not good at exams!
She's known to speak casually, even to vicious-looking folk
I wanna get full marks!
Shirai!
She is an office lady who skillfully hits a calculator and counts perfectly
No way!
She realized her dream, the destined Fukei
Fukei will live on forever
Yamaide!
A 'Discipline-woman' who maintain the peace of Sakura Gakuin
Listen!
She unconsciously speaks Kagoshima dialect when she is off-guard
Sensei, sensei! Aiko is furtively having an ice-cream again!
Megu! You snitch on me again? I'm gonna blow you up!
Hey, hey, hey, if you want to know about us
Are you following?
Our appeal lies both in our appearances and the gaps between
Observe the steady progress of our feminine power!
Let's strive to become “Super Ladies”!
Jump (High!) Jump (High!) Jump! Jump! Jump! (High!)
Kurashima
She deals sternly with her homeroom teacher who forgets her name
Oh!
Kokeshima the magician, with her illusions
I can't stand your forgetfullness anymore
Kurosawa!
Salutation (properly)
Stare (steadily), She is an old hand 'TV-Fighter'
So skillfully looks into the camera which is shooting her
Yes. My name is Kurosawa Mirena
Okazaki!
Never be fooled by her neat-and-clean appearance. She is always full of energy
Tou!
She is expanding her repertoire of funny-face and impersonation
Mori-sensei, give it a try!
Okada!
From Mikawa province she has invaded, a knowledgeable history buff
I know it!
She is wont to quote historic hero while she spins
Today I quote Toyotomi Hideyoshi-san. "Open the window...the outside world is huge"
Hey, hey, hey, if you want to know about us
Are you looking on intently?
Our appeal lies both in our appearances and the gaps between
All worldly things are but ephemeral, Let's brush up on our feminine power!
Let's strive to become Super Ladies!
Jump! (High!) Jump! (High!) Jump! Jump! Jump! (High!)
Then, I shall call the role!
3rd grade of middle school
Isono Rinon
Genius
Ooga Saki
Certainly
Shirai Saki
Açaí
2nd grade of middle school
Kurashima Sara
Hai
Kurosawa Mirena
Grazie
1st grade of middle school
Okazaki Momoko
Poyo〜n
Okada Megumi
All right!
Yamaide Aiko
Thank you
6th grade of elementary school
Asou Maaya
Nyan!
Hidaka Marin
Hello
Shoutoubu gonen
Fujihira Kano
Yay
Yoshida Soyoka
Glasses!
Well then, remaining members, please introduce yourselves!
Hidaka!
I've never been abroad, but let me handle the English-language matters
Song for smiling
She stares at a point -- seeing someone whom we can't see
It's a Dream
Yoshida!
She popped out of anime world, a 2-dimentional girl with glasses
She opens a small window and shoot you through your heart
Garagara bakkyuun!
Fujihira!
She can't stop her chattering, as always
Guess what?
She is very short, so she has a lot of potential
What's the meaning of 'potential'?
Asou!
With curry? (Of course!)
With beef-bowl? (Absolutely!) Red-pickled-ginger
She plays her skillful kendama perfectly and shows her smug face
Everyone, I wanna show you my specialty, Kendama
Hey, hey, hey, if you want to know about us
Do you get it now?
Our appeal lies both in our appearances and the gaps between
Observe the steady progress of our feminine power!
Let’s strive to become Super Ladies!
Hey, hey, hey, if you want to know about us
We'll tell you!
Our appeal lies both in our appearances and the gaps between
"All worldly things are but ephemeral" Let's brush up on our feminine power!
Let's strive to become Super Ladies!
Jump! (High!) Jump! (High!) Jump! Jump! Jump! (High!)
In conclusion, we are the "Limited to the growth period" unit
Sakura Gakuin!