Now, I shall do the roll call!
Welcome! I am Mori Hayashi, homeroom teacher of Sakura Gakuin.
The last concert of the 2015 nendo has started!
Everyone, are you hype- ow, ow, ow, ow, what are you doing?!
Stop getting in my way while I'm talking!
How's it going everyone?
This is the last concert of 2015
Are you ready to get hyped?
The are coming out from behind you!
Everyone look behind you!
People sitting on the first floor, are you guys ready?
How about the second floor?
Third floor, are you well?
People at the live viewing, how are you guys?
Alright everyone hurry up and get up here!
If we don't take attendance I'll make you take the year over!
Okay, we're all counting on you! Make sure you do it right!
This is this year's Sakura Gakuin!