Reflecting in the mirror that day was a dazzling silhouette
I stood there, longing for that lovely figure
It became a habit to chide and scold
the part of you that stuck out from that “innocent” comment
Even if we don’t say anything, somehow it still gets through
These emotions and this nervousness are all your doing, aren’t they?!
As we laugh together lots and motivate one another,
the feelings that pile up in layers are a mille-feuille
A rainbow-colored harmony is playing
Saying good bye to clumsy-me who shed tears out of frustration.
Now I can say it without crying:
"Bye, see you again tomorrow"
Lately, you’ve just been gazing up at the sky
You tell me of your endless dreams with unwavering eyes, but
when you undo your ribbon, it’s a sign that you’re turning into an adult
Don’t go away and leave me behind, complaints like that feel like slipping out
When your knee is side by side with mine, I get fired up
With the warmth you transmit me, my bluffing heart melts away gently
As we play with each other lots and even as we get mad
this mille-feuille of feelings won’t collapse
This pride of mine won’t be broken, not by anyone
Absolutely! want to convey it in my own fashion
Even if I’m incomplete, I’ll say it without any embarrassment:
"Thank you, always"
We carried the matching cellphone-straps as a proof of beginning of our friendship.
their color has faded since when you gave it to me, but...
As we laugh together and motivate one another all through our lives,
I want our friendship to pile up layers, like a mille-feuille
All over the world, a rainbow-colored harmony
Saying good bye to clumsy-me who shed tears out of frustration.
Now I can say it without crying:
"Bye, see you again tomorrow"