How can I say...
Can I talk a little while?
I'm sorry but I also have something to say
It's a very strange feeling
Er...I though I would feel sad
But actually, I'm very happy now
That's because of the atmosphere these three seniors have established
I just think so.
Honestly, I think I kept speaking very badly of these three girls
like "an idiot who knows nothing"
"A bombshell girl who you should avoid to deal with"
or "a very clumsy working lady"
I really talked trash about them a lot
But honestly, even with so much trash talk,
I've been always partial to the three of you
These three seniors in this nendo have a strong inclination towards variety shows
and they kept relying on me, they kept listening to me seriously
I always felt I was very lucky to be their teacher especially in this one year
Actually, as you know, I'm not an outstanding person
When I had been an active comedian,
I had one-tenth or lower name recognition compared to that of Miyoshi or Matsui today
(You don't have to say such a thing now)
I was not well known, really
I had one-hundredth of BABYMETAL's ability to attract an audience
(rather, it was one-thousandth)
Yes, it was one-thousandth
Such an ordinary person like me can teach you something because I made a lot more mistakes than you
and because I had setbacks after I tried my best with my comrades
I think that experience enabled me to teach you something
Thus, you guys must know, you should make a lot of mistakes
It's good to make mistakes
and it's also good to have setbacks
I regard my setbacks as my treasure
So I hope you'll make a lot of mistakes that will show you a good michishirube (guidepost)
The experience will guide you
That's also true for the graduates who came here
except for the would-be nurse
Nurses can't make mistakes
It's life-threatening for a nurse to make a mistake
Well, I think the one and only condition to be a Superlady is,
--and I don't really care about other conditions--
the sole condition to be a Superlady is to become happy.
Even if you obtain high popularity,
or even if you become very wealthy
that has nothing to do with the matter.
In any event, you'll be a Superlady as long as you're happy
Please become happy. I hope for nothing more.
By the way, I've been very happy in this year. I remember
the night when Ooga got a huge round of applause at the Rakugo class
the night Isono kindly ate the wasabi for me
and the night Shirai told me she wanted to be like Mori-sensei
I was so happy in those nights.
So, I can safely say, in this year, or in these five years
that I was entitled to be a Super Boy, having taken a step ahead of you
From my heart,
I want to apologize to Isono for making a long speech
I tried to make it as short as possible
As for what I've left unspoken,
I'd like to talk about it in the LoGiRL program tomorrow
I apologize
Honestly, I want to have a job which makes people smile together with these girls
So please be in touch
Thank you very much
And now,
Graduates,
you are dismissed
Everyone, please give them a round of applause
With that, the 2015 nendo Graduation Ceremony of Sakura Gakuin has ended
Everyone, bow