Next, a response speech from the graduates.
Sakura Gakuin's Middle School Third-years, if you please.
Yes!
Student Council President Isono Rinon acting as representative.
Farewell response:
And so it has become the season when all things have gone quiet and the sakura bloom.
Already we have sent off thirteen graduates,
But now the day has come when we ourselves must graduate Sakura Gakuin.
We took for granted all the things we got to do with Sakura Gakuin,
The fact that we will no longer have these things after tomorrow hasn't sunk in for me.
Still I find myself wondering if we twelve are about to dance together tomorrow and after.
The very first year after I transferred in as a 5th-grader, I was the youngest member.
Now I'm middle school third-year.
As a senior member, I've been showered with supports and expectations of so many people.
and that made me stand before you now.
The first show I ever appeared in, from that moment on,
began my life as a student of Sakura Gakuin.
When I was the youngest member, I just dedicated myself to the lesson of my beloved dances everyday.
gathering multitudes of experience,
and I tried to keep up with the senpais
who were walking in front of me
And once it came the time that we no longer had our senpai in front of us,
in our final school year, our worries were numerous.
This year's seniors all transferred in in different years:
Myself in 2011, Saki in 2012,
and Shi-chan in 2013,
so honestly, I can't say we had been getting along very well till we turned seniors.
But once it was us three leading Sakura Gakuin,
we proved ourselves able by coming together in solidarity, and we managed to get through it a step at a time.
Among the events of this 2015 year for Sakura Gakuin was a record of six transfer students entering.
As such, the start of 2015 was marked by confusion and worry.
As the first and foremost instruction, we told transfer-ins the mental attitude as a Sakura Gakuin member.
At first, It was hard to understand for young girls and we got frustrated a lot.
But, we're very determined to send kouhais what we've learned from senpais,
to make kouhais carry the good tradition of Sakura Gakuin
and we spoke with them on this topic time and again until they understood the message.
We were very glad to see them all catching on little by little.
Because this year's group was half transfer-ins,
this year provided us with a newfound number of rewarding experiences.
Soyo
When I saw you overcoming your self-doubt in your ability bit by bit,
it made me happy and encouraged me as well.
I hope that you will be able to improve your skills even further.
Kano
You seem shy at times, but I think there is much about yourself which you are keeping hidden.
So next year, please show us a side of Kano which is yet unknown to us.
Marin
When you first transferred in, it was as if you could not speak at all due to shyness.
But when I look at you now, the way you interact with everyone instead of acting alone,
the way you speak with all of us, makes it apparent that you have changed greatly since you transferred in.
Please lend your unique worldview to Sakura Gakuin.
Maaya
You are tall, but you have the face of a child.
I think it to be one of your better qualities, seldom though you show it, but I am also very fond of your composed demeanor.
Next year, when you have become a middle school student, I want to see you become more like an elder sister.
Momoko
I know you're actually a very hard-worker.
and have your own opinion in several things which you seldom tell us.
And I know you have made an effort to understand everything we taught you since the first day you transferred in.
because I know how hard you've been trying, I would like for you to improve your excellent dancing further.
I believe you can do it in a way that only you can, and I look forward to it.
Mirena
As a middle school second-year transfer, I imagine you also faced your share of pressure.
Even though you just transferred in this year, you will still be a senior next year.
You tried not to show your worries, but I have noticed it.
I think only Mirena can understand the mind of the new transfer-ins fully.
I hope you become a good senpai who is considerate to the feeling of transfer-ins
In this year, we often saw you became a peacemaker among new transfer-ins. So I know you can do it.
Megu
This year, the way you dealt with your kouhai made it seem like you have matured.
Time and again you astounded me with your grace.
I hope you can pass on your grace to kouhais as a Sakura girl.
And when you speak, because there will be times when you can see things objectively,
I hope you refine your talking and can show your personality more next year.
Aiko
Next year you will be the longest tenured member of Sakura Gakuin.
I know you realise the mind of senpais well.
You should know better than any the goals of a senpai.
Especially for things like the meaning of song lyrics and choreography,
please pass down the traditions of Sakura Gakuin to your kouhai.
Sara
Next year you will be a third-year in middle school.
You really shined while we were charging through the last leg of this 2015 year.
I know how much consideration you have put into Sakura Gakuin and how much concern you have for the group.
The time has come to carry out what you've thought.
If you can convey your feelings to those around you, then everyone will prosper as you do.
and give a vigorous reprimand to bad. I hope you can be such kind of a senior.
In the context of this year's changes, I have come to know the value of our graduates.
I often consulted the graduates because I did not want to present my weakness to kouhais.
And I received a lot of advice from them.
It is on account of all the graduates that we can be on this big stage.
I am grateful for your watching over Sakura Gakuin all this time.
But even so, I think the greatest source of strength for Sakura Gakuin is the fukei-sans.
I still can clearly recall the faces I saw when I looked out from the stage at my first performance.
As the years went by, I could see more and more flags. I am so grateful to so many people who come to know Sakura Gakuin.
Being able to stand on this stage as part of Sakura Gakuin
and being able to perform are things we should not take for granted.
To the fukei, the graduates, the staff,
and our teachers, we're grateful for your support, without which we would not find ourselves in this setting.
Through the many experiences we had as members of Sakura Gakuin, we could reinvent ourselves.
We will continue to smile our best to strive for our own paths to becoming super ladies.
Even if we part, we will be united, and we will not ever forget the fukei-sans,
and the time we spent in Sakura Gakuin will become a treasured memory.
I truly thank you for what you have done for me so far.
Please continue to support both us and Sakura Gakuin henceforth.
Twenty-seventh March, the 28th year of the Heisei Era,
2015 Sakura Gakuin graduates' representative, Isono Rinon.