Give me a moment....I'm sorry
Farewell address
Finally, the long and severe winter has ended
and the beautiful Sakura flowers began to bloom
Rinon-chan, Saki-chan, C-chan
Congratulation on your graduation
It seems like just yesterday
Sakura Gakuin 2015nendo started on May
I feel it like a dream
that almost one year has already passed since then
Looking back on this year,
we've made so many memories
On the day on May,
when we had a photo-shooting,
we met the transfer-ins for the first time
as many as SIX girls
All of them were so energetic
I had had only one year career as a Sakura girl,
but honestly,
I suspected that it's difficult to keep the good tradition of Sakura Gakuin
I found three of you seniors
were also with an anxious look on your face
But before long,
you showed us your hopeful attitude
toward making new Sakura Gakuin
rather than the anxiety
Three of you have been kind and generous
but once in a while, you taught us strictly
how to make the very best performance with 12 of us
or how each member can make an improvement
Your harsh words made us realize
that we had been neglecting the effort to improve ourselves
or that we had been just satisfied with what we used to be
We were annoyed by our own simple-mindedness and sometimes shed tears
Shirai Saki-chan, the Talk Chairperson
She is 15, but she is said to be like an office-clerk
as this, she is matured in her appearance and mind
and she is kinda smart
So she is likely to be seen as a down-to-earth girl
But actually, she sometimes is clumsy and goofy
For example, she sometimes stumbles over nothing and falls down
or, she once dropped and lost her bank-card
When she runs, she leans forward and looks funny
And, C-chan is...
not only a member of Sakura Gakuin
but also a dedicated Fukei-san
Because of her Fukei-sb...Fukei-spirit,
she is highly observant to each one of members
far higher than I expected
She has been looking at us so carefully
that she once asserted "As for the MCing, I know..."
"what you're good at,"
"and what you're bad at"
Just before a concert,
she gave us good advice on
what we should talk on the stage
Every one of us loves such caring C-chan
C-chan,
you gave us wonderful advice from the perspective of  a customer
which is hard to know for us
We could realize several things thanks to your advice
and that motivated us a lot to entertain Fukei-sans more
Thank you
Ooga Saki-chan, the Education Chairperson
She once poured barley tea into her glasses-case, half-asleep
And in our streaming program LoGiRL,
she so often give strange and funny answers at quiz-segment
She has strong feelings for singing
and sometimes she sang so emotionally that the song sounded like an Enka-ballad
At a break time in a lesson,
she sometimes started to play with elementary schoolers
and she looked just as if she herself had been an elementary schooler
Saki-chan as the Education Chairperson
always tried to face each member sincerely, truthfully
And when we consulted her for something,
she tried to put herself in our shoes
and gave deep consideration for us
Among three of seniors, Saki-chan has been
the girl of the most severe words
And she was determined to create the best stage
even though that made her disliked
or made her being scared
But we could always feel your love
when you gave us the harshest words
Saki-chan
Sara had believed myself to be bad at singing
and honestly, I had disliked singing
But, without noticing it, I became to
hope to sing carefree, in my own way like Saki-chan
You made me love singing
When I consulted you for singing skill
you encouraged me saying "You definitely can sing in a new way!"
Sara surely will improve myself in singing
Please watch over me
Thank you
And Isono Rinon-chan, the President of the student council
She can't read difficult kanji, much less write it
And she so often knows nothing about what an ordinary girl knows
She is very picky about vegetable
When she was forced to drink the veggie smoothie
as a penalty at the Transfer-ins Orientation event on June
the girl of no tears happened to cry
Such Rinon-chan whom we don't see how to make cry
is really, truthfully a kind girl
She said "I'm trying to
send something important directly in a way easy to understand
for the young girls who have little vocabulary
She also said "I don't want to show my weakness"
"because I'm the senior now"
She carried out her word and has been a cheerful Rinon-chan
without showing her frustration or sorrow
Rinon-chan,
Sara want to learn a lot more
about Sakura Gakuin in these five years from you
so that I can carry the good tradition to kouhais
So, please keep being a good friend
and a wonderful senpai of us
On the day before a concert,
Rinon-chan and I made a sheet of setlist for the dressing room
and you told me the history of Sakura Gakuin
or your mind while making the sheet
That moment was really precious
and fun for Sara
Thank you very much
Next time I go to Sakura Gakuin,
when I enter the studio and give "Good Morning",
I'll not find three of you...
I can't take...
the fact. I don't want to think about it
Honestly, I feel very lonely
for your graduation
But...What we must do now
What we can do now is...
to keep good tradition of Sakura Gakuin
which senpais had created
and to see you off with smiles,
together with Fukei-sans, Mori-sensei,
Principal Kuramoto-sensei and staff teachers
Until now, we cried a lot
got scolded a lot, got angry a lot
Everything is my treasure
Thank you very very much
And, congratulation on your graduation
on March 27, Heisei 28 year,
Current student representative
2nd grade in middle school, Kurashima Sara