H₂O, Look, inside of me
Is a helix that keeps being drawn on and on
E=mc² conditions I keep to myself
CO₂, That’s right, right now you
Spit out a sigh, and try to speak
Even failure becomes good substance for tomorrow
Deposited in the body is a semiconductor
A conductor that transfers feelings across
I’ll predict this love’s fortune with my litmus paper
A mixed-up friendship heats up. Thermal reaction
The direction of my gaze. A measuring cylinder
Those feelings of mine are growing on, a petri dish
Science Girl, Silence Boy
Even if Aristotle couldn't see through them
The secrets
Science Girl, Silence Boy
The basis for our being alive together here
Is surely hidden
H₂O₂ What's done is done
No point in worrying about it. In the meantime,
mankind just heads into the future
In the cobalt blue sky, the chime rings
He becomes lighter like helium and flies away
Even ignorance is his energy, he gets carried away!
I'm feeling both anxiety and hope
Our hands connect like a molecular structure
Because you're here, I can become stronger
Science Girl, Silence Boy
Even Einstein couldn't come up with it
A dream
Science Girl, Silence Boy
The moment we're living here
I'll show it to you someday
Science Girl, Silence Boy
The secrets