Amidst the white light, greenery sprouts on the mountain range
you start flying toward the distant corner of the sky
The endless blue sky moves your heart
To the bird dashing toward freedom, without looking back at all
Gather your courage onto your wings and ride on the wind of hope
Entrust your dream to the vast sky
I suddenly recall the nostalgic voices of my friends
The times I cried because of meaningless squabbles
The joy I felt in my heart, the days we embraced each other
Those days are gone, but I’ll hold on tightly to those memories
Gather your courage onto your wings and ride on the wind of hope
Entrust your dream to the vast sky
Now is the time to part, believe in the future you’re taking off to
Believe in the energetic power of youth
in this vast, boundless sky
Now is the time to part, believe in the future you’re taking off to
Believe in the energetic power of youth
in this vast, boundless sky